let questionData = [{
  question: "What color is the wall in Monica's appartment?",
  answers: [
    'Red',
    'Blue',
    'Purple',
    'Yellow'
  ],
  correctAnswer: 2
},
{
  question: "What does Joe not share?",
  answers: [
    'Money',
    'Beer',
    'Women',
    'Food'
  ],
  correctAnswer: 3
},
{
  question: "Where were Ross and Emily supposed to go for their honeymoon?",
  answers: [
    'Vermont',
    'Athens',
    'Amsterdam',
    'London'
  ],
  correctAnswer: 1
},
{
  question: "What was the name of the bald headed girl who Ross dumps for Rachel at the beach?",
  answers: [
    'Bonnie',
    'Joanna',
    'Monica',
    'Jasmin'
  ],
  correctAnswer: 0
},
{
  question: "What does Chandler's co-worker, Bob, think Chandler's name is?",
  answers: [
    'Muriel',
    'Toby',
    'Mike',
    'Joe'
  ],
  correctAnswer: 1
},
{
  question: "What is the name of the potential boss that Rachel kissed accidentally?",
  answers: [
    'Mr. Zelner',
    'Joanna',
    'Jack',
    'Mike'
  ],
  correctAnswer: 0
},
{
  question: "Joey says that giving Rachel pickles during her pregnancy is like giving him what?",
  answers: [
    'Salami',
    'Beets',
    'Fries',
    'Salad'
  ],
  correctAnswer: 3
},
{
  question: "What does Ross call Cute Coffee House Guy?",
  answers: [
    'Dingo',
    'Mister T',
    'Hums While He Pees',
    'Ugly naked guy'
  ],
  correctAnswer: 2
},
{
  question: "According to Joey's sperm bank file, what rules?",
  answers: [
    'Sandwiches',
    'Beer',
    'Knicks',
    'Food'
  ],
  correctAnswer: 2
},
{
  question: "Finish this quote. 'If I met her in a bar, I'd be...'",
  answers: [
    'Dancing with her',
    'Buying her drinks',
    'Asking her number',
    'Buying her breakfast '
  ],
  correctAnswer: 3
}]

export default questionData;
